{
  "LevelId": 31,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 314,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "SYMBOLIC",
      "question": "erm describes something that represents or stands for an idea, concept,"
    },
    {
      "id": 315,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "STRIKING",
      "question": "that describes something that captures attention or is visually impressive"
    },
    {
      "id": 316,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "LAUGHTER",
      "question": "the joyful sound people make when amused"
    },
    {
      "id": 317,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "OVERSEAS",
      "question": "geographical direction would you find a location that is not within your home country"
    },
    {
      "id": 318,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "LAGGARDS",
      "question": "individuals or entities that are slow to adopt new technologies or innovations"
    },
    {
      "id": 319,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "LANGUAGE",
      "question": "use to communicate thoughts, ideas,"
    },
    {
      "id": 320,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "MOMENTUM",
      "question": "the quantity of motion an object possesses"
    },
    {
      "id": 321,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "AIRPORTS",
      "question": "facilities are designed for the arrival, departure,"
    },
    {
      "id": 322,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "LONENESS",
      "question": "describe the state of being isolated or feeling a deep"
    },
    {
      "id": 323,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "LITERATURE",
      "question": "written or spoken works that express ideas, emotions,"
    }
  ]
}